all right so in this video i'm gonna be
giving you guys the mindset on how i
made a hundred thousand dollars in a
week like that's something that maybe
five years ago i thought i was gonna do
but obviously i'm gonna give you guys
the exact plan preparation on how i did
it um so make sure to watch the video
all the way to the end because i give
you guys gems that i've never given i
always do chart breakdowns for you guys
but this is a little bit different
because charts is one thing but then the
mindset and the planning behind it is
completely different so let's get into
the video alright so right now we're on
the way to the airport um if you guys
saw what i posted uh two weeks ago from
today uh sensei and i we uh basically
decided like yo let's do like a quick
collab i had like a 25k day sensei had
like a 17k there like he did something
where he made some money he's like bro
let's give away some cash so
um all you had to do was just follow
both of us and then um tag three friends
in the picture and then somebody from i
don't think it's like dr or pr i don't
know he won and then we said anybody
whoever wins will fly them out to miami
so we're on our way right now to the uh
airport uh pick up the giveaway winner
we're gonna give him ten thousand
dollars in cash so i got the boy sensei
uh behind me following me we're gonna
pull up to the airport um
he said he landed like 30 minutes ago
we're in the middle of like rush hour
we're pulling up right now to the
airport to uh give him the money and
take him to his hotel i think he has
family here he was telling us he's
probably gonna spend the weekend with
his family um and yeah so let's go pick
him up at the airport i don't speak
english i'm sorry
so so the giveaway winner seeks spanish
so obviously we both speak spanish so um
we decided to vote is you have your cash
in there
sorry i don't speak english only spanish
i hope i hope he's not taller than me
he's following me man
what's up bro
bro he's taller than me i don't like
really tired
retired i had to fly to puerto rico
first yeah yeah there was some flight
from santo domingo
to here so
i had to go to puerto rico first like
wait like three hours and then comes up
here man i'm dead
but you make money so you're good bro
you're good
all right we're good
this is from us
and then you get this and then you leave
right now costs too much money already
bro that's just for you you do whatever
you want
all right the video's done let's go
can i take him now to the hotel he's
gonna stay here i think his family lives
here and then um yeah we're probably
gonna go eat and yeah bro appreciate you
for participating
i hope that helps you man bro appreciate
it yeah thank you
we really gave that guy 10 grand i don't
even think he knows how to speak english
this guy bro i mean but you haven't paid
me so
huh you haven't paid me yet so i hope
that money wasn't
no no you're good you're you're locked
in you take crypto right uh yeah because
i don't got for you
we literally gave this guy a heart no
if we give him a 100k
he said that he had to take a flight
from uh puerto rico to come over here
because there wasn't like a direct
flight from dr
to miami so he went from dr puerto rico
and puerto rico to miami so um now we're
going to take him to his hotel right now
you know what's great but i thought he
was going to speak in spanish so i was
like oh i got to put him out of
subtitles
he's cool people i still don't know his
name but
i think his name is dan then that daniel
oh
yo yo appreciate you bro
you are you held me a big time with me
[Applause]
so that was a little intro giveaway that
i did with my boy sensei so literally we
do giveaways all the time on instagram
so make sure to follow us on the ground
because uh that one was just pretty
random uh we just posted a picture and
then we said like comment and share and
tag three friends and we're gonna give
somebody away ten thousand because i had
a pretty big trading day i'm like you
know what let me just give it back to
somebody so yeah this guy won randomly
and we didn't want to give him the money
like to his country he said he wanted to
like come over so we flew him out and
then we gave him the cash uh he stayed
here for one night and flew back over
there with all the money so um yeah that
was like a little intro but with that
being said uh in this video i'm going to
give you guys the five barriers five
tips that you need to have these in
order to make big days like i had right
so yes i did make a hundred thousand in
about seven eight days technically six
trading days right so
number one is going to be your account
size so
let's be realistic i made six figures
because i had a six figure account i
didn't flip it from a 10 000 account or
500 account like that is not realistic
like i'm sorry i will be that person to
tell you the truth that is not gonna
happen yes i'm sure you guys have heard
stories of people flipping you know
sixty thousand to like two point six
million or some crazy stuff like that i
recently just saw somebody post on
youtube uh somebody took ten thousand to
one point five million i'm like we're
like that's insane just because that
possibility is there yes like it is
possible doesn't mean that it is
sustainable now you can probably do it
once maybe twice but then after that
like your psychology is out of the
window so definitely rule number one is
you need to have the right account size
i aim anywhere like when i do these
account flips to have you know a
specific percentage of my account size
but i don't recommend if you don't have
the same equal account size to reach for
anything over that so let's say you have
a thousand dollar account if you want to
do some crazy challenge like this reach
to have a take profit of a thousand
dollars so you would like make 100 of
your account if you don't have either a
funded account or if you don't have a
large size account these type of profits
are not realistic if you guys want to go
get funded make sure to go check out
level of society funding people all the
time right so number two would be the
platform that you're trading on so the
platform that you're trading on is
probably like crucial because there is
spreads commission slippage like imagine
being fifty thousand dollars in profit
and then when you go close the trade it
only saves your twenty thousand dollars
in profit like that that would piss me
off like very bad so you need to make
sure that the platform you're trading on
is trustworthy if you guys wanna know
the broker that i personally traded this
on and i've been trading for quite a
while on and i continue to keep scaling
my uh my phones on make sure to click
the link below that's what the exact
broker that i use where i did this
account flip and i plan to do many many
more things so definitely need to trust
the platform you're on because spreads
can eat you up commissions can eat you
alive and then at the same time
slippage you can be x amount in profit
and then that can really get cut by half
so you realistically didn't make that
money just because the platform you're
trading on isn't trustworthy number
three would be patience patience
patience patience like because i
announced this on my instagram right
like i just out of the blue to my
followers i was just like all right guys
next week i'm gonna make a hundred
thousand dollars like i didn't just say
that out of the blue just because i woke
up and i felt like it like i waited for
the markets to align a specific type of
way where i know that the markets were
going to head where they started
momentum that way due to the fact that i
was patient enough to wait for the
markets to align like that you guys need
to understand that i didn't just wake up
and say all right this is the week where
i make a hundred thousand you have to be
patient without being patient like it's
just not gonna happen right so i waited
for my setups to come to me because uh
let's say you do set yourself to have
let's say a goal like this whether you
want to make a thousand a week or five
thousand a week whatever goal you want
to set for yourself and let's say it's
wednesday london session like damn it's
already wednesday and i haven't taken
any trades i have to make a trade today
like i have to do something today in
order to reach that profit and that's
not the case because at that point
you're forcing a trade you're not being
patient you're just taking a trade to be
involved you're taking a trade to reach
that goal but maybe thursday night on
london you get a nice trade setup you
risk the right amount and then it
literally makes you reach your profit
you need to understand not every day is
a trading day so patience is key that
leads me to my number four which is
emotions emotions and patience kind of
fall in the same line slash not really
because you can be very emotional when
you're winning and you can be extremely
emotional when you're losing when you're
losing it could be you think you know
this is like this is it this is the last
day of your life you know this is where
you're praying to god this is where
you're you know in your prayers crying
whatever the case is like that is so bad
because nobody is torturing more your
own mind than yourself like bro i can
guarantee the markets don't even know
what you're doing the markets don't even
care that you're being emotional they
don't care that you're crying they don't
care about any of those things and
having this emotional attachment to
something that is just on a screen is
very unhealthy due to the fact that no
matter how much care how much love how
much passion you have towards those
charts they're not going to give you
anything in return because it's just a
computer computer has no emotion so you
can give it all this drive all this
positivity these you know you can like
candles all over the computer whatever
you want but that doesn't matter like if
the trade makes sense it's going to go
if it doesn't make sense it doesn't go
if you lose you lose because you risk a
certain amount if you win it's because
that's the reason why you took the trade
let me say that again if you take a
trade and it wins it's that's the reason
why you took the trade you wanted the
trade to win but if you lose a trade
well that's fine that's why you risk a
certain amount before you take the trade
like you need to understand that every
single loss needs to be completely
controlled and then your profits have a
random outcome little trick for you guys
um whenever i take my trades i always
put a stop loss um always like no matter
what but i never put it take profit i
always put a visual take profit on my
trading view and i set alarms and then i
just forget so whenever trades is going
into profits i'm just monitoring and
profit moving my stop-loss modifying it
but i never want to cut my profit short
i always want to cut my losses short but
never my profits and this is something
that over the time like is where i kind
of you know got the whole set up forget
and it just removes all emotions of it
because once you start like if you're
taking a tray that's going with the
trend why would you cut it short you
want to keep it going with the trend so
that's why this is something that i've
learned over the time and if you
practice this yourself you notice that
your emotions will go out of the window
because you're just letting the trade do
its thing and that leads me to my last
point which is strategy and risk
management so what was your risk
management on taking this trade how did
you scale in so many times all right all
right so let me explain to you guys you
guys need to understand that what i did
in this week of trading i'll pop up
another screenshot here of my results
this is not something that i do on the
regular this is something that i plan
that i pre you know set a specific
amount size on the site like something
that was calculated i didn't just go in
and just did this you know just like a
free-for-all right so very importantly
when it comes to doing these types of
account flips is strictly risk
management without risk management your
account is gone first trade because you
want to make the flip so fast you need
to understand i'll split my account in
four i'll split my account in six it
really depends so let's say the trade is
an a plus trade setup i'm like i bet i
want to split my account in four and i
only want to risk 25
on this trade but not the full 25
goes on one trade i'll chop up the trade
in three so let's say it goes into my
profit i will break even then i'll scale
in in another position so that 25 gets
chopped into three and then it's just
different multiple entries that's why
you might see different entries on the
same move because one i'm going with the
trend
two obviously it's my strategy it's a
you know trade that's worth the risk and
then three i'm playing with the house
money i'm not playing with my money at
that point anymore if i'm taking a trade
while it's in profit trade comes back
takes me out of break even or i take
profit on whatever the case is i'm not
losing my account stays at the same i'm
playing with positive equity so this is
something that you obviously have to
learn how to master um it's very easy i
recommend you guys try it out with a
demo account you guys could create an
account with the broker that i used
below and then just try with the demo
account it doesn't hurt like demoing it
out is not going to be an issue like it
should be actually a good thing because
it shows that you're taking the business
seriously if you come in just wanting to
deposit 100 bucks and then you know
risking the 400 bucks trying to get 500
that's not the right risk management
that is not the right emotional control
you're not having patience and you're
just not being realistic with yourself
this is a business that's going to take
you time
like endless nights like what i did
today is something that i dreamt of
doing maybe like five years ago and i
didn't just pop up one day and did it
like it's something that i built up into
like i really need you guys to
understand that um but yeah definitely i
would say risk management without having
that like you didn't even i don't want
to say that you don't need to have the
right trading strategy obviously you do
but you cannot have the best trading
strategy you can still be working on it
and then with the right risk management
you'll stay in the game like the whole
point is you want to stay in the game
you don't want to just you know run into
the field and just get shot one shot no
you want to like take your time go
around the barrels and like play
according to your plan because as you're
risking this risk management you're
learning your strategy you're making
modifications you're staying in the game
to keep adjusting to that plan because
if you're going in too fast and it just
you know just goes out the window so i
hope this video was helpful for you guys
um if you guys want to see an actual
breakdown of like all the charts uh that
i trade like i can literally break down
every single trade that i took on a
chart and like go back obviously in time
with the on trading view and show you
guys why i took it the reason that i
took it how i managed it um if you guys
want to see that video make sure to drop
a comment below uh make sure to turn on
notifications and subscribe because i
got a lot of cool videos coming in the
next couple of weeks and uh yeah this is
uh kind of the mindset of the things
that uh you need in order to get
obviously these type of results but
please understand that it does not come
in the same week you start training your
same month like it takes time guys so
i'll see you guys in the next video take
it easy guys
[Music]